[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[Haran] Huh?
EPISODE 11
[chuckles softly]
THANKS FOR THE
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Kang Hyeokchan…
KANG HYEOKCHAN
GLASS TUBE
Why is this name here?
Hospitalized? Hyeokchan?
He hurt his hand badly in the lab.
He even got surgery.
How does he know Hyeokchan?
OUTSIDE THE LAB
"Lab"?
[Chan] NaClO.
Sodium hypochlorite…
[officer] I guess
you majored in that field.
It seems like you majored
in engineering, not art.
Huh?
This is…
[Sujin] I'm only visiting, so I'm not
authorized to treat patients directly.
I came from Boston.
[stutters] Boston?
[sighs]
[Seok] There was
an international conference.
Your school…
-No, your former school…
-[Chan] That's enough.
Boston Institute of Technology.
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
[Genius huffs]
Ah.
[sighs]
Is she upstairs?
THANKS FOR THE
-[line connects, ringing]
-[inhales sharply]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense music playing]
KANG HYEOKCHAN, GLASS TUBE, BLOOD
KANG HYEOKCHAN HOSPITALIZED, WOMAN
THAT SOUND WAS HER BRACELET
[exhales shakily] No…
[Hyeokchan]
Let me tell you something cool.
My dorm roommate is Korean,
and his name's Chan, too.
[Hayeong] You used to call him Chan.
Your old boyfriend, Hyeokchan.
Hyeokchan's roommate
was Seonu Chan?
[vibrating]
SEONU CHAN
[Chan] Watch out!
Song Haran!
[Haran] I met you for the first time
a few days ago.
How long have you known me?
Tell me how you know me.
What are you hiding?
He's known me
for seven years.
[door closes]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ somber music playing]
[Haran] He knew my face
and my name.
It's nice to meet you.
Ah…
I saw you up close earlier,
looking at the Sisley painting.
No…
This can't be right. No.
Hey, it smells like rain.
[Chan] That's the smell
of organic matter diffusing.
Petrichor.
[Haran] There's another guy
who speaks like him.
She doesn't like eggplants.
[Haran] How do you know
I don't like eggplants?
Yuck. The taste of neon alien.
I'll eat those for you.
The neon aliens.
Then…
all those messages…
were him pretending to be Hyeokchan?
[exhales shakily]
No…
That can't be. No.
He'll explain everything.
No…
This doesn't make sense.
[♪ music continues]
-[cell phone vibrates]
-[Chan] Let's meet.
Let's meet up and talk.
I'll explain everything.
No, please…
Please.
Please…
It must have gotten mixed up
in my stuff back then.
Just consider this pen
a pen that I found for you.
I think you owe me an explanation.
I bought the same pen…
when I was in the States.
Then this pen…
He knew everything…
[breath trembling]
[sighs]
[♪ music fades]
-Hey…
-[Haran] Don't come any closer.
Boston Institute of Technology.
Kang Hyeokchan's roommate.
Have you really known me
for seven years?
[breathes shakily]
-Song Haran.
-Don't say my name.
[breath trembling]
Did you have fun
pretending to be Kang Hyeokchan?
[breath trembling]
Seonu Chan,
who are you?
[high-pitched ringing]
The Seonu Chan
I liked and trusted
until just a few hours ago…
Who is he, really?
[yells] Who are you?
[♪ emotional music playing]
[stutters]
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have let you
find out like this.
I should've told you…
No wonder you were so flustered
in front of the doctor.
You didn't want to get caught,
because she knew you were in Boston.
Because I couldn't find out.
-I'll explain everything.
-Tell me.
Did you message me
seven years ago,
pretending to be Hyeokchan?
Is that true?
Answer me.
Did you really deceive me
and pretend to be Hyeokchan
behind his back?
I'm sorry.
[breath trembling]
Why?
Why did you do that?
Our laptops
got switched once.
[sighs in disbelief]
[exhales shakily]
Did you have fun
chatting with me like that?
Did you build some kind of fantasy
and start liking me?
I can't even tell
which was really Hyeokchan or you…
The pen.
The engraving.
Who was it?
Was it you or Hyeokchan?
-I'm sorry.
-[exhales shakily]
If that's fake…
[sobbing] Even if this pen is fake…
Then what was I holding onto
the past seven years?
I even hurt my grandma
because of all that.
Why…
You should've at least told me
when you gave me this pen.
When I believed you like a fool,
you should've told me the truth.
I needed time.
My memories aren't…
[sighs exasperatedly]
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Do you even know what it meant
for me to hold your hand?
To open my heart to you?
[sighs] How could you, of all people…
How could you, Seonu Chan?
[sighs dejectedly]
I'm really sorry I hurt you
by making you find out like this.
I won't ask you
to believe everything I say,
so please…
I was surprised that there was someone
who believed in me this much.
I was grateful.
But you knew me all along.
You knew what hurt me the most
and what would break me the easiest.
I thought…
you were like a miracle to me.
But to you…
I was just an experiment.
[Chan sighs dejectedly]
It's not…
No…
[♪ music fades]
Haran, that's not true.
Never.
If you were fake,
you shouldn't have made me like you.
You shouldn't have made me
trust you this much!
I didn't even know it was all fake,
and I foolishly laughed, cried,
and was happy because of you.
[Haran sobbing]
It must have been so fun watching me.
Like a spring picnic.
[Chan pants]
Wait.
Please.
[panting] Please, let me explain.
Explain what?
That you were still sincere?
That's so obvious.
No matter what you say about it,
the truth won't change.
Everything was fake from the start,
and every moment you spent with me,
you were hiding that secret from me.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
I knew it was too good to be true.
There's no way
someone like me could be that happy.
Whenever I feel like I'm really happy,
I lose someone.
[young Hadam] Hi!
-[Hyewon] Hi.
-[Junho] They look so excited.
[tires screech]
Dad!
[Haran] Mom and Dad, 13 years ago…
[gasps, sighs]
Just five minutes left.
-[people clamoring]
-[siren blaring]
[Haran] Hyeokchan, seven years ago…
And today.
You, Seonu Chan.
This is the kind of ending that suits me.
I'm not allowed to be happy.
You've proven that once again.
[breath trembling]
Haran, please.
If we end things like this,
you'll go back
to putting up walls around you.
-If you do that because of me--
-You're right.
You just pushed me back into winter again.
My past seven years, the present,
and the future.
[♪ music fades]
You've ruined it all for me.
[sighs] Just let me go.
You disgust me.
[♪ mellow song playing]
[breathing heavily]
[sharp inhale, groans]
[sobbing]
[Haran] Is it still valid?
Being friends. The three-month trial.
Then let's do this.
It'll be like we're on a spring picnic.
Let's have fun.
Ms. Song!
You're Designer Song Haran, right?
[Haran chuckles]
[Chan] I'll wear this every day.
[Haran shudders]
[Haran chuckles]
[Chan] I feel like I'm in a dream.
[chuckles softly]
[♪ song continues]
[inaudible]
[wind whooshes]
-[leaves rustling]
-[birds chirping]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
-[♪ song fades]
-[pens clatter]
[objects clattering]
SEONU CHAN
[sighs]
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
[Haran] I'm not allowed to be happy.
You've proven that once again.
You just pushed me back into winter again.
My past seven years, the present,
and the future.
You've ruined it all for me.
It's my fault…
I have to do something.
[exclaims softly]
Talk it out with Haran.
If you're sincere,
I'm sure she'll understand.
[♪ music continues]
[sighs]
[♪ music fades]
-[knocks on door]
-[Hayeong] Haran?
What's going on?
Why are you cooped up in here again?
How is this scarf? Should I wear it?
I'm heading to work in 10 minutes.
Do you want to…
What?
You're sweating.
Haran, you're burning up.
I told you to dress warmly, didn't I?
-Let's go to the hospital.
-I can just take medicine.
Medicine won't be enough right now.
You should just rest today…
How can I when Grandma's away?
I'll get dressed, so get the car ready.
[Hayeong sighs softly]
Oh… Let's talk.
[pants] I know you don't want to see me…
[stutters] but just hear me out.
If we end things like this,
you'll go back to how you used to be.
All right.
You don't have to look at me
or listen to me.
So please, just look at this.
-[Chan stutters]
-How many pills should you take?
-Oh? It's Chan.
-Don't open the window. Just go.
-But it's Chan.
-Just go.
Okay.
If he came all the way here,
it must be pretty important.
What's going on? Did you have a fight?
Let's just go quietly.
He looks so down, though.
[Hayeong sighs]
Let's continue after lunch.
-All right.
-[groans]
[Haran] Can you--
It's Chan.
Hey, Chan.
Ms. Song.
I don't have any meetings today.
Don't let anyone in.
[Sol] Huh? But Chan…
[Chan] I won't make any excuses.
I know you don't want to listen,
so please…
No exceptions.
Don't let anyone in my office.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[hesitates] I'll buy lunch today.
Why don't you join us since you're here?
No, I'm okay.
Ah.
Please give this to her.
Don't tell her it's from me.
[Raemee] Okay.
He looks more sick than her, though.
[sighs]
[♪ music fades]
Does this one stand out too much?
[Seunggyu] It'll feel more like noise
than a focal point.
What do you think?
I agree.
Then let's stick to the flow instead.
-All right.
-Good.
Oh. But has anyone
seen our robot, Mr. Yeon?
I have to ask him
about our press cut deadline. [sighs]
I haven't seen
his perfectly groomed hair for days.
He must be incredibly busy
taking care of things for Ms. Kim.
Right. He'll be busy
making up for her absence.
But when did Mr. Yeon
start working in Nana Atelier?
Since he was 19.
[Seunggyu, Sol, and Raemee gasp]
-Nineteen?
-[in English] Legend.
[Sol exclaims, whines]
[in Korean] But no matter how busy he is,
he does seem to have disappeared.
-[Seunggyu] Mmm.
-Right.
It's like he just quit.
[Sol gasps] What if he really did?
[♪ mellow music playing]
[Sol] He could have,
if he's been working since he was 19.
[♪ music fades]
I organized the color differences
and confirmed the pigment.
I also picked the other SS looks.
And you need to approve this.
How are you feeling?
-I should ask the same thing.
-What?
You look really unwell.
-Oh… I just have a light cold.
-That's not all, is it?
What is it?
Has Mr. Seonu gotten worse?
No, nothing's wrong. [chuckles awkwardly]
Just focus on your condition
before your surgery.
Don't worry about me or the company.
Mr. Park, you can head home today.
I'll stay here.
[Manjae] Mmm-mmm.
I told you I'm in charge here.
You should hurry home and rest.
[Nana] You might end up
getting hospitalized instead of me.
You look like you'll collapse.
Go home.
Then please take care of her.
Thank you, Mr. Park.
[in English] My pleasure.
[chuckles]
-[in Korean] Bye, then.
-Bye.
It seems like something's up.
Ms. Kim Nabong, worry about yourself
until your surgery.
Hmm?
[therapist] Is this okay?
Yes, it's okay.
-Tell me if it hurts.
-Okay.
[therapist]
You're checking with him again.
Of course. I should record this every day.
He has to pass
the medical test in February.
Then let's check your ankle now.
Try pulling with strength.
[therapist inhales sharply]
It doesn't hurt?
No, not at all.
[gasps] Your range of motion
has improved a lot since last week.
Right, Doctor?
[therapist] Yes. [chuckles]
Then, next week,
we'll fit you with an ankle brace
and work on standing up.
Don't strain yourself. Good job.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
That was two degrees more than last week.
Are you sure it didn't hurt?
I know my body better than anyone.
I feel like I'll be able to get up soon
and start throwing balls.
[chuckles]
Mr. Cha, you really have
exceptional recovery speed,
-as expected.
-[clears throat]
Then let's start
outdoors practice tomorrow
so you don't lose your touch.
Yes, Coach. Let's do this.
[both chuckle]
-[cell phone vibrating]
-Ah.
-Hang on.
-Sure.
Hello?
Come in.
Are you just going to leave again?
Mr. Yeon.
I've failed you again.
I've never protected you properly.
[breath trembling]
I'm sorry.
So,
were you going to wait until I recovered
and try to quit again?
Like that day, 13 years ago?
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Good job. You can go now.
Ms. Kim…
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I'm sorry, Ms. Kim.
If only I hadn't been sick that day…
If I'd been the one driving…
I couldn't even repay you
for your kindness.
I'm sorry.
If you have time to talk such nonsense,
use that time
to prepare for college.
You'd better get accepted in one try.
[♪ music fades]
You made that same face
after Hyewon and Junho's funeral.
When I met you for the first time,
do you know why I told you to come see me?
You reminded me of my past.
Even if no one noticed,
I did my best
and worked so hard on my own
in Paris when I was 20.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
As soon as I turned 20,
I flew to Paris alone
with no friends or family.
I threw myself
into both studying and love.
But I suddenly got pregnant
and gave birth by myself.
I struggled so hard
attending fashion school,
carrying a baby on my back.
I told myself that someone
would notice my efforts someday,
and I pushed through.
[sobs]
[Nana] Once I succeeded,
I felt so much pity
and pride
for myself back then.
I saw you that day,
and I felt the same way about you.
That's why I reached out a hand.
Because I wanted to acknowledge
your efforts.
You…
took care of me…
and changed my life, but…
I never thought of it like that,
but you've already repaid me enough.
Without you,
neither I nor my company nor my family
would have gotten this far.
No.
I…
I don't have the right to stay…
Taeseok.
Put down that burden now.
You couldn't have prevented the accident
by driving that day,
nor could you have prevented this
by noticing more quickly.
No one in my family
blames you for what happened.
You've been holding onto that guilt
because you're too kind.
But you don't have to do that.
-[sobbing]
-[Nana] Put it all down now.
You've done a great job so far
working by my side.
So stay with me.
[sobbing]
[Taeseok crying]
[young Hayeong] Mr. Yeon.
[young Taeseok] I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
I…
shouldn't be sick.
[Taeseok crying]
[footsteps approaching]
[♪ music ends]
Do you want one?
[Hayeong sighs]
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to eavesdrop,
but I brought fruits for Grandma
and ended up overhearing.
Ah. So that's why
you were at Mom and Dad's grave.
Okay. I understand now.
-I'm sorry.
-Stop saying you're sorry.
Like Grandma said,
none of us have ever blamed you.
Not for a single second.
Mom, Dad. It's not his fault, right?
You heard that, right? They said no.
[sighs softly]
[Hayeong] Here.
Have this sweet and sour candy
that you love so much…
and leave all your burdens behind.
[chuckles softly]
Have this
and cheer up.
-You're giving this to me again.
-What?
Didn't you give me one last time?
Did I?
[winces] It's so sour. Why is it so sour?
[chuckles]
[♪ heartwarming music playing]
YOU SAVED ME TOO
[Haran sighs]
[Chan stutters]
No exceptions.
Don't let anyone in my office.
[sighs softly]
[coughs, sniffles]
[cell phone vibrating]
MR. PARK
Yes, Mr. Park.
What's wrong with your voice?
Did you catch a cold?
Oh…
Maybe it's because you're not here.
[chuckles softly]
I have no one to talk to,
so I guess my voice is a bit rusty.
[clears throat]
[inhales sharply] Is…
something the matter?
Besides the fact that I miss you,
everything's fine.
It must be tough at the hospital.
I'm doing well here with Genius,
so don't worry
and take care of yourself, too.
All right.
[cell phone beeps]
[Genius whining]
I'm okay.
No, I'll make sure everything's okay.
Everything will be okay.
Song Haran.
[♪ music fades]
You saved me,
seven years ago.
You saved me back then!
[Chan panting]
I'm sorry.
Seven years ago and now,
I've wanted to show you the real me.
I should have told you, no matter what.
[Chan sighs]
It's all my fault.
Please, just look at this.
Everything's in here.
Stories that you don't know
about back then.
Let me ask you two things.
Just say yes or no.
If I look at this,
will it change the fact
that you pretended to be Hyeokchan
and messaged me…
seven years ago?
[♪ melancholy music playing]
-No.
-[Haran] Then,
does it change the fact
that you kept this secret from me
the whole time…
while you were with me?
-Haran.
-Say yes or no.
No.
-But--
-Then it won't change my mind.
If those two facts don't change,
then whatever explanation you give
or whatever you do,
it won't change my mind.
If you still think the lies you told
can be explained by something,
then you still have no clue
how you've shattered my heart
and how you've destroyed
the past seven years of my life.
Don't ever show up in front of me again.
When I see you,
I feel like I'm going to lose my mind
thinking about the seven years I lost.
[Chan] I won't even
think about staying with you.
But you'll go back
to how you were seven years ago…
[breath trembling]
[high-pitched ringing]
[groans]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
-[exclaims] Cha Yougyum!
-[clears throat]
Your pitching is still amazing.
No wonder you were always named MVP
at every tournament.
[Hadam chuckles]
[inhales sharply]
[grunts]
Oh, gosh, I missed it.
[sighs softly]
Hadam, let's stop.
You must be tired.
I'll ask Changmo to help me later.
No. We can do it.
Let's go.
All right, throw it.
[grunts]
Gosh, I missed it again. I'll go get it.
[sighs]
[sighs worriedly]
Did we overdo it?
You must be tired.
Not at all.
I know my body best.
[inhales sharply] I feel much lighter now.
Oh, right.
My team's visiting later,
so it's going to be really noisy.
You should head home now.
Then I should go and study rehabilitation.
Have fun with the guys.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
[sighs dreamily]
Those punks.
I should give them some snacks.
Hmm? It's pretty quiet, though.
[Yougyum sobbing]
[♪ emotional music playing]
[umpire] Out!
[players cheering]
FINAL, CHEONGSOL HIGH 3
HANEUL HIGH 2
[sniffles]
[stutters] Yougyum.
[Yougyum] Hadam…
What do I do?
[breathes shakily]
I…
I don't think I can make it.
I know my body better than anyone.
[Yougyum crying]
CHEONGSOL HIGH SCHOOL WINS
[♪ music fades]
What is it?
Can't you sleep?
Should I turn the light off?
No.
Manjae,
you should go home.
Go and sleep comfortably.
[Manjae] I'll go once you're asleep.
But why can't you sleep?
I just…
have a lot on my mind.
Goodness.
It's snowing.
[Manjae] Oh. It is.
Why do you have a lot on your mind?
You know I've been tough
since I was little, right?
But…
thinking about going under anesthesia
and getting surgery
makes me feel a bit nervous.
I'm sure the surgery will go well.
Just be yourself, the strong Kim Nana,
and get through this.
I'm more worried about something else
than drilling a hole in my skull.
What is it?
I have to shave my head here.
That would ruin my look.
Why does that worry me more?
[laughs]
You really are the Chuncheon fashionista.
This won't do.
I should protect your look.
Hang on.
What?
Oh, my.
This is hand-knitted.
Did you really…
[♪ lighthearted music playing]
[Manjae] I knitted it in secret
while you were sleeping.
But I think I'm a knitting genius.
-I followed along easily.
-[gasps]
I might have to open
a knitting workshop in my coffee shop.
-Huh?
-[chuckles]
How did you…
Would you like to try it on?
Wow.
You look beautiful.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Let me see.
-Okay.
Here, look.
[gasps, giggles]
-[chuckles]
-Nabong.
After the surgery,
why don't you rest
by my side?
What?
[Manjae] Kim Nabong.
It took a long time,
but will you begin
your second "La Vie en Rose"
with me, Park Manjae?
Hmm?
Manjae.
You've been through so much all this time.
So get some rest
by my side now.
[♪ music ends]
Hey, roomie.
Why are you sitting there in the dark?
Hey.
Is something wrong?
She…
found out about everything.
I didn't have the chance to explain.
It's all my fault,
but she's the one suffering
when she did nothing wrong.
It hurts so much
to see her in pain…
[scoffs] But I must be crazy.
Despite everything,
I still
want to see her so badly.
[Manjae sighs]
If I lose her like this,
if I…
make her return to her old self,
then…
[sighs dejectedly] Then…
Oh, dear…
I did wonder if something was wrong. Gosh.
[mumbles]
[exclaims softly]
You're burning up.
How long have you been like this?
-Huh? Oh?
-[Chan sighs]
[exclaims worriedly] Hey! Roomie!
Hey!
Chan!
Goodness.
[Chan] I want to stay by her side
in spring, in summer,
in fall, and in winter.
I want
to stay by her side,
but I don't know what to do.
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
Do you need someone to talk to?
Ah…
I made some assumptions,
but there was a lot more I didn't know.
You must have had
such a hard time until now.
You've been through a lot.
I want to tell her everything
and stay by her side,
but if I tell her about myself,
it will hurt her.
I'm not even sure
if I can explain myself to her
without reopening
[sighs]
her old wounds.
But if you're this sincere,
don't you think
she'll realize it in the end?
To be honest, I'm scared.
If I act rashly,
my flawed memories might ruin everything.
I'm scared…
I'll hurt her again.
Chan.
After living all these years,
what I've learned is that
waiting until everything's perfect
isn't always the answer.
For people and for love.
[in Latin] "Memento Mori."
[in Korean] You said
you don't want regrets.
If you keep waiting,
you might lose your chance
and regret it later.
Why don't you show her
how sincere you are first?
It won't be too late
to take care of other things later.
[♪ music continues]
[Chan] I should get ready
to explain myself to her.
I should start
by what happened seven years ago
and tell her in my own way.
[♪ music fades]
[shudders] It's so cold.
Why are you brooding out here in the cold?
What time is it?
[Hayeong] It's past midnight.
How long have you been here?
You're already unwell.
Come inside.
Oh, uh… Did you go to the hospital?
Haran, what is it?
Huh? Is something wrong?
What's going on?
-Hayeong.
-Yes?
I want to wake up.
I thought I was in a dream until now,
but I guess it was a nightmare.
[♪ somber music playing]
I want to wake up,
but I don't know how.
-Haran.
-We're not meant to be together.
I have to forget things
that seem impossible to forget.
But I don't know
how to get over everything.
[Hayeong sighs softly]
[sighs]
-[ice cubes clacking]
-[Hayeong sighs]
[Hayeong grunts softly]
[thermometer beeps]
[sighs in relief] Her fever dropped.
Gosh…
[grunts softly]
[♪ music fades]
What?
Gosh. What time is it?
NOV 29 SAT
Are you here?
What?
Where did she go?
Haran!
-[sighs wearily]
-[line connects, ringing]
[cell phone vibrating]
HAYEONG
[panting] What?
Where did she go?
[cell phone vibrating]
DESIGNER SONG HAYEONG
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[cell phone continues vibrating]
[groans softly]
[sighing]
[groans softly] Hey, Hayeong.
Chan, sorry to call you so late.
But did Haran contact you?
[grunts] Why? What's wrong?
Haran's gone.
The car's gone,
but she's not at the office either.
You're the only one
I could ask where she could be.
I feel so anxious after what she said.
She said she was in a dream,
but it was a nightmare.
[breath trembling]
[♪ tense music playing]
-I think I know where she is.
-[Manjae exclaims worriedly]
Where are you going?
You're still burning up.
I have to go find her.
It has to be me.
[stutters] What are you saying?
Did something happen to Haran?
Huh? Chan!
[♪ music continues]
[Hayeong] She said
you're not meant to be together
and that she has to forget it.
I couldn't understand what she was saying,
but she's really sick right now.
[Chan] I feel like I'm in a dream.
[Haran] Those words sounded a bit sad.
It sounds like
they're not meant to be together.
-[engine revving]
-[navigator beeping]
[breathing shakily]
[Haran] I said I won't ever forget
this moment.
Ah, and in spring…
[Chan] Let's go see
the cherry blossoms in spring.
We'll have shaved ice in summer…
Oh, and go to the beach.
We'll see the autumn leaves in fall,
and in winter,
it would be fun to go snowboarding.
[♪ music fades]
-[engine revving]
-[navigator beeping]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[grunts]
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[grunts]
[Hyeokchan] Do you have any idea
what you've done?
-[Sujin] You must've jumped at the chance.
-[Haran] I love you, Chan.
Kang Hyeokchan.
Did you have fun…
[grunts, exhales heavily]
[high-pitched ringing]
[♪ music fades]
[tires screech]
[Chan breathing heavily]
[♪ pensive music playing]
HADONGDO-GIL
[breathing heavily]
No…
Please…
[♪ dramatic music playing]
It can't be…
No way…
Please…
There is no way I caused it.
[Haran crying]
[Chan] But what if I did?
Then she…
[♪ music swells]
[Haran bawling]
[inaudible]
-[♪ music fades]
-[PA beeps]
[indistinct announcement on PA]
[sighs]
I wanted…
to check something for the last time.
Seven years ago…
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
…on the day of the accident.
Did I…
hit Kang Hyeokchan?
Did I hit him and make him fall down?
Is that why his lip tore
and the waste container fell down?
Is that true?
Yes.
You hit Hyeokchan.
But why?
[Sujin] Don't you remember?
The day he came back from his trip,
you told Hyeokchan everything.
[door closes]
[♪ music fades]
Long time no see.
-Right.
-Hang on.
[sighs] Sorry about this.
We need to switch laptops back.
Move all your data from my laptop.
Oh…
Well…
I…
I have something to tell you.
You do? What is it?
[Chan] Uh…
While you were away, I--
Will this take long?
Yes, a bit.
Then let's talk later.
I have to meet my professor right now.
I'll see you, uh…
in the lab later.
[sighs softly]
Right. What is it?
You needed to tell me something.
Your messenger…
What?
While I was using your laptop,
I kept chatting with your girlfriend.
What?
[♪ tense music playing]
What are you talking about?
Say that again.
We ended up
chatting after that.
But she thinks it was you.
[chuckling] Hyeokchan,
you left your earphones in my car…
[Hyeokchan] Are you saying
you've been talking to Haran
while I was away?
Pretending to be me?
Sorry. It's all my fault.
[sighs]
Hang on. [sighs]
Who are you to do that?
Why would you ruin everything like this?
Tell me. What sort of things
have you been saying?
Why?
Did you think it was okay
since I asked you a few times?
You were someone nobody even cared about.
Did you get excited
that someone paid attention to you?
[Chan grunts]
-Kang Hyeokchan!
-[groans softly]
[Sujin] You had your eye
on Hyeokchan's girlfriend, Song Haran.
You told him
that you'd been chatting with her
while he was traveling,
so things got heated.
And you ended up hitting him.
[breath trembling]
Can you still say
you didn't have feelings for her then?
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Then…
[breath trembling] that accident…
Was it because of the container that fell?
[Sujin] Yes. So how do you feel?
Does it feel good to know the truth?
I told you,
nothing good would come
from digging up the past.
It was all because of you.
You caused the accident,
and it killed Hyeokchan
and hurt a lot of people.
Don't act like it's some grand love story.
You just tried to steal
Hyeokchan's girlfriend
and caused the accident that killed him.
That's all you are.
[♪ music swells]
Do you have any idea what you've done?
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
It was all my fault.
[♪ music fades]
Where in the world did you go?
You even left your phone behind.
You think I wouldn't worry
if you disappeared like that?
[Hayeong clicks tongue]
I was so worried.
You'd better not do that again.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
Ah. What about Chan?
Don't even mention him to me anymore.
I mean, didn't you meet him?
He heard you were gone
and started his car right away.
-Didn't you see him?
-What do you mean?
I called him late last night
because I didn't know where you were.
-I thought he might know.
-[sighs]
He said he knew where you could be
and left right away.
Maybe you missed each other.
Don't contact him about me anymore.
He has nothing to do with me.
His phone's off.
[sighs]
[Chan] I couldn't react properly.
-[car honk echoes]
-[high-pitched ringing]
It's hard to tell
where sounds are coming from.
[sighs]
What is it? Where are you going?
Where are you going?
This patient was transferred
after a lab explosion in Boston
seven years ago.
He was treated for full-body burns,
and shrapnel is still lodged deep
in the temporal bone.
It's a high-risk area, so we are only
monitoring it at the moment.
He also has unilateral hearing loss.
Burns? Shrapnel?
He visited the ER recently
after a brief loss of consciousness
and minor bleeding.
The outpatient clinic will check
if it's related to the shrapnel.
That really is a difficult spot.
[presenter] That's right.
If his bleeding
was caused by the shrapnel,
it may be accompanied
by neurological symptoms
such as auditory or visual hallucinations.
There have even been reports
of memory distortion
in severe cases like this.
[♪ pensive music playing]
The patient with the shrapnel
in the temporal bone…
Did he take the exam?
No, it's past his appointment,
but he hasn't shown up.
But why do you ask?
SEONU CHAN
It's nothing.
[♪ music fades]
Mr. Park.
Mr. Park, did you see…
[sighs]
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
[Chan] A three-month trial!
Just try me out as a free trial.
As soon as the three months are over,
I'll disappear without a trace.
[breathing heavily]
END OF TRIAL
[♪ music ends]
We can proceed
with the model fitting as revised.
[Raemee] Spring is here!
Spring is here!
Look, spring is here.
-The forsythias have started blooming.
-[Hayeong gasps]
The forsythias are blooming?
That means we're on a tight schedule.
All right, let's hang in there
for a few more days.
-Let's do this!
-I'm so sleepy.
-[Sol chuckles]
-[Raemee] Goodness.
[pen scraping]
[Haran] The seasons of life
don't come in order.
[sighs softly]
It really is spring.
Sometimes, when you think it's spring,
winter suddenly arrives.
Take this.
Oh…
Then let's do this.
It'll be like we're on a spring picnic.
Let's have fun.
[♪ soft emotional song playing]
SUMMER, SEVEN YEARS AGO
IT STARTED WITH WALLS
END OF TRIAL
[Haran] The man
who suddenly lit up
my cold winter last year
like radiant spring sunlight…
disappeared from my life.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
[Haran] He disappeared.
The Seonu Chan I know
would never leave like this.
[Sujin] He disappeared because of me.
-I did something I shouldn't have.
-[bracelet clinks]
He's been preparing for a long time.
It's gotten so bad
that there's nothing they can do.
-[Chan] Do you remember…
-[Haran cries]
…how I was trapped in winter for so long?
I knew you'd understand
my sincerity.
[Haran] Seonu Chan, where are you?
Where on earth are you?
[♪ song fades]
[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park